var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which country is completely landlocked by The Republic of South Africa?",
    correct: "Lesotho",
    choices: ["San Marino", "Namibia", "Pretoria", "Cape Town", "Angola", "Mali"]
  },
  {
    question: "Of the 48 continuous U.S. States, which State has the longest coastline?",
    correct: "Maine",
    choices: ["California", "Oregon", "Texas", "Florida", "Washington", "Michigan"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has the world's longest coastline?",
    correct: "Canada",
    choices: ["Russia", "Australia", "Japan", "Indonesia", "Argentina", "Norway"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which country borders the most other countries in the world?",
    correct: "China",
    choices: ["Russia", "Paraguay", "Slovakia", "Laos", "Switzerland", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    question: "French is an official language of how many African countries?",
    correct: "28",
    choices: ["7", "32", "11", "9", "13", "21"]
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest country by land area in the European Union?",
    correct: "Denmark",
    choices: ["France", "Germany", "Sweden", "Italy", "Spain", "Estonia"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which two countries share a land border?",
    correct: "France and the Netherlands",
    choices: ["The U.K and the U.S.A", "Spain and Germany", "Italy and Tunisia", "Greece and Germany", "France and the U.K", "The U.S.A and Japan"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which U.S. state is in both the Eastern and Western hemispheres?",
    correct: "Alaska",
    choices: ["Hawaii", "Nebraska", "Maine", "Florida", "North Carolina", "New York"]
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following countries has territory on 2 continents?",
    correct: "Turkey",
    choices: ["Djibouti", "Yemen", "Sudan", "Mexico", "Greece", "Canada"]
  },
  {
    question: "What two countries share the largest land border in the world?",
    correct: "The U.S and Canada",
    choices: ["Sweden and Norway", "Algeria and Mali", "Brazil and Argentina", "Brazil and Venezuela", "The Democratic Republic of the Congo and Cameroon", "China and Thailand"]
  }
];
